[
    {
        "question": "مايليو",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "يمان",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يفول",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيريا",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتسا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "وراتمه",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايفيولا",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليون",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "يليار",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لا",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "وال",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارادام",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يشتيروي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يشتاتيا",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يبوت",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارابون",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يافيل",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اماريشاه",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "وتوروب",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوسوي",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "مير",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايروديم",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديك",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "اساكيم",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "وزندا",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غنيو",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناهيشنيت",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناهوكيب",
        "response": "بيكوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "يجاكيزاك",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اياريج",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يجاكيزاك",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يموكوك",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويغ",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويشت",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يروساس",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "وكوزين",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اريكا",
        "response": "اكيرا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يجين",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتسا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ازيل",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايوغاك",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "انيه",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكولا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتانيه",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "وستنيز",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "وكوغنير",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يافيل",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتروك",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكوسيه",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "سونا",
        "response": "انوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "ناغوكايب",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
       "question": "وكوش",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "وكيد",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "يماي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "سناجناف",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
       "question": "سويلوي",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "وغوموست",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
       "question": "يمانان",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "نزيا",
        "response": "ايزن"
    },
    {
       "question": "يكاراز",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
       "question": "اراهاروا",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
       "question": "يونيا",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "واهوغ",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
       "question": "نيليريك",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
       "question": "وروستانيه",
        "response": "هيناتسورو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ليشتير",
       "response": "ريتشيل"
}
]
